adserverplus.com 2008-12-17

# Oridian - Online Media Solutions

Privacy 

* * *

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Effective date September 1, 2005

This privacy statement applies to the Oridian web site and to our ad-serving network.

Online Media Solutions, LTD. is an online advertising network of worldwide publishers, from desktop applications to web sites.  
Oridian provides its publishers with a complete interactive advertising solution, including ad serving, professional client services, and performance statistics. Each publisher implements their own solution, and controls all communication to Oridian’s servers. 

This privacy statement details: 

| > | What personally-identifiable and non-personally-identifiable information is collected from you through the website and/or our ads  
---|---  
> | How the information is used  
> | With whom the information may be shared  
> | How Oridian’s ad-serving works  
> | The kind of security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control  
  
If you have questions regarding this statement, contact [privacy@Oridian.com](mailto:privacy@Oridian.com). 

**DEFINITIONS**  
Our publishers provide media space where ads are displayed, and our advertisers provide the ads to run on our media.  
Publishers:  
Our publishers are web properties. Web properties consist of a select group of websites that have authorized Oridian to display advertisements on their site. Advertisers:  
Our advertisers provide ad creative in various formats that are displayed on our network of publishers. Advertisers are responsible for ad content as well as the link from the ad. 

**COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
There is no collection of personal information on Oridian.com. Oridian does not collect personal information through its ads on its publisher network of web properties. 

**COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
There is no collection of non-personal information on Oridian.com. Ads served on Oridian’s network of publishers collect advertisement-related information only. This information includes aggregated performance records such as which ads were displayed, how many impressions they received, and which, if any, did the user click on.   
While you are browsing a website that includes Oridian’s Java tag, we monitor only ad creative rotations and your clicks, if any. This information is aggregated on our computers log files for the purposes of reporting to advertisers and ad sales organizations the performance of their ad campaigns and is never focused on a specific user.   
According to the standards of the Internet advertising industry, third-party ad servers associated with our technology may make use of cookies. Cookies, by default, are enabled in the browser, and you can disable them at any time via your browser preferences menu.   
Oridian utilizes your IP address to determine your country of origin in order to serve ad content relevant to your country and language. 

Third Party Privacy:   
This privacy statement does not cover the privacy practices of Web sites linked from the Oridian network, from advertisements displayed on the Oridian network, or of third-party ad servers. Additionally, according to the standards of the Internet advertising industry, third-party ad servers on Oridian’s network may make use of cookies. Cookies, by default, are enabled in the browser, and you can disable them at any time via your browser preferences menu. 

**INFORMATION SHARING OR DISCLOSURE**  
As stated before, no personal or non-personal information is collected on Oridian.com. However, our ad-serving network collects non-personal information pertaining to ad performance, which is disclosed only to the relevant advertisers and publishers. This information is disclosed to advertisers and publishers in aggregate form only, and never pertaining to individual users. It is used to provide performance statisticsabout advertisements and creatives, and to serve as a basis for payments.  
Please note, however, that any information is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. 

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
Oridian has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect all information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Our employees are made aware of and are accountable for compliance with our privacy policy. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any material changes in this policy we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our website. For questions or concerns about the information collected or used at this site, please contact [privacy@Oridian.com](mailto:privacy@Oridian.com).

CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE  
If all or part of the company is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the aggregated performance information you may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, Oridian will take steps to assure that the personal information is used in a manner consistent with Oridian’s privacy policy.
